One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
The Height of Folly
All ships, prepare for bombardment!
Retreat! Retreat!
All soldiers, evacuate the island!
Board your ships!
"JUSTICE"
What happened at the center of the island?!
I don't know! We'll just follow the order!
St. Saturn! Admiral Borsalino!
It's dangerous.
Please proceed to your ship promptly!
Kizaru and I will stay here.
As soon as preparations are complete,
commence bombardment!
What?! But...
Go.
Yes, sir!
Won't this...
Won't this all be over
if you just kill me?!
St. Saturn!
Egghead...
...houses the latest research findings
from every field of study!
If you destroy it, scientific progress
will be set back by 100 years!
Revoke the Buster Call!
Please, Kizaru!
Is there something more
you are hiding from us?
That is probably...
...also troublesome
for the World Government.
We do not need progress!
I'm begging you!
For the sake of humanity!
Oh...
I forgot to tell you...
It is about the ship
that escaped the island yesterday.
I have already issued an order
to pursue and strike it.
Because there might be someone aboard
who learned something about the Void Century.
To make sure none of them survive...
I sent a warship.
How could you do that?!
They don't know anything!
They're innocent people!
You got them involved, Vegapunk!
Just like the people of Ohara,
you broke the law...
...succumbed to the urge for discovery
and delved into the past.
Pacifistas, remain on the island!
Other soldiers, get to your ships!
As soon as preparations are complete,
we’ll commence bombardment!
Ship 54, prepared!
Ship 21, prepared!
We're ready to fire!
Hurry! Get in the Vacuum Rocket!
While Vegapunk is distracting them!
The meeting point
is the rear entrance of the Labophase!
We'll leave Egghead
once everyone has arrived!
Okay!
Sanji! What about Vegapunk?!
Don't worry, Bonney-chan!
I'll get him!
We’ll leave it to you, Sanji!
Count on me!
Nami-san, it's me! What's your status?
We're already at the rear entrance!
What's all the noise down there?!
Labophase
Well...
Back
entrance
What?!
The Buster Call?!
This island is finished!
How many times are we gonna have to
deal with a Buster Call?!
I'm worried about Stella...
Swiftly!
We gotta run! Hurry up, everyone!
Robin!
Everything's fine,
so you can keep resting.
Sanji-kun? What is Luffy doing?
He's there, right?
Franky and Bonney went down there, too!
He's not in my sight, but he's fine!
Tell me the status on your end!
Zoro is still being held up by Lucci...
Jinbe is heading there
to put a stop to that.
If we leave Zoro, he'll get lost.
And...
...Brook went to help Lilith,
who remained at the Sunny.
But there is a problem.
The escape plan to have the Vegaforce-01
carry us from here is no longer viable.
Because it was destroyed by Kizaru!
What?! Then how do we escape from here?!
Well...
Looks like Brook has an idea...
Well, to me,
moving a ship over land is a piece of cake!
This is amazing, Bone!
With this,
we'll reach the rear entrance in no time!
Freezing Island Clouds and letting the ship
slide on them was a great idea!
It's an honor to be praised
by the world's greatest genius!
This is fun!
And how are we going to stop?
Oh, I haven't thought about that.
We're going to fall then!
What are you going to do?!
What should I do, Lilith-san?!
Think of something already!
The barrier is still up at the Labophase.
All ships!
The target is Egghead's urban area.
Destroy the central factory
and the future city!
Start firing!
Wait! We haven't boarded yet!
W-Watch out for the Pacifistas!
Egghead...
Departing Fabiriophase, bound for Labophase.
We are now departing.
All right!
Let's go, Vacuum Rocket!
Launch!
What the hell is this?! So fast!
The transit duration is 32 seconds.
Sacred Murakumo Sword.
Damn Kizaru!
Bonney-chan! I'm coming!
Pacifistas.
Shoot Bonney and Kuma...
...dead!
It is just exquisite!
The daughter he sacrificed himself to save...
...is now being slain by his own clone.
What utter foolishness.
A fitting end for the insect she is...
It is the height of folly!
Dad!
Bonney...
When I heard you became a pirate,
the worst possible scenario
flashed through my mind.
It is, by the Navy's command,
the Pacifistas in your father's likeness...
...shooting you...
...without recognizing you
as their daughter!
Bonney-chan!
I can't eat anymore...
Hey! He's Straw Hat, isn't he?!
Oh no...
I can't move, I'm too full...
Capture him now! He's an Emperor of the Sea!
Escape vessel destruction failed...
C-Contact Kizaru-san...
...and tell him they are heading for Egghead!
Look at them goin’ at it!
Just like the paper said!
He digested all that food?!
He might devour me if I get closer...
So he's not human after all?
That was close!
Oh no! We're about to be
engulfed in flames!
We can't stay on this island any longer!
Though he is an Emperor,
we'll all do it together!
On the count of three,
we'll put Sea Prism Stone cuffs on him!
One, two, three!
Board your ship!
Move! Move!
Egghead is done for!
Burn everything down
starting from the shore! Shoot!
Kuma! Bonney!
Hey! Can you hear me, Atlas?!
Shoot that foolish family,
once and for all!
Atlas! Tell Bonney!
Bonney-chan!
I got it, Stella!
Bonney!
Atlas!
Don't shoot!
Dad!
Help us escape...
...from this island!
Hm? What's wrong?!
I think I heard a voice...
What?!
How can you hear anything
in this deafening noise?
What?
H-Hey, look at the Pacifistas!
Why are they turning this way?!
The Pacifistas have gone rogue!
I had only one concern.
Bonney.
I was worried...
...that you might be killed
by your own beloved father.
Kuma.
I was worried...
...that you would harm your beloved daughter
with your own hands.
That is a tragedy I couldn't allow to happen!
That is why I...
...programmed something
into all the Kuma lookalike units.
So...
...even if he is given commands
by the world's highest authority,
even if he turns the whole world against him,
Bonney,
Kuma will always...
...be on your side!
This is just a selfish wish of mine!
So...
...I know well...
...there are unavoidable consequences...
...for doing such a thing!
Vegapunk!
Dammit! Vegapunk!
Eliminate them, Kizaru.
Immediately!
Kizaru!
Damn!
I'll cut you both in half.
This won't hurt, Bonney.
Straw Hat?
Where is he?
Full belly, full power!
This is getting fun!
Bonney-chan, are you okay?!
The island is wiggling!
We have a bigger problem!
Stop the Pacifistas!
Vegapunk!
Vegapunk! Let's run!
You'll be killed!
This rhythm...
Nika?
Yes, he is my hero.
He will come laughing,
moving to this rhythm.
Bonney...
So you didn't realize it...
I couldn't be certain either,
until I saw it for myself.
The very Straw Hat Luffy
who Kuma had his eyes on,
was Nika, the Sun God!
What?
Kuma was right...
The Buster Call is futile.
Because there are people all over the world
who have been waiting for him...
...for centuries!
Northeast
coast
Egghead
We're off the northeast coast!
There is a humongous ship approaching us!
That's definitely them!
But I thought they disbanded
over 100 years ago!
Why are they here?!
Should we stop?!
No, we'll charge ahead!
They're coming this way!
Shoot!
Damn! Why are the Giants here?!
They keep asking "Why," Dorry!
Don't they know that everything in this world
happens for a reason, Brogy?!
We're here for you, Straw Hat!
Sun God!
Emergency!
The Giant Pirate Crew has appeared!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru